How do you catch a killer you've already caught?
The Traveler is a horror, thriller film directed by Michael Oblowitz.
On a dark Christmas Eve in a small town, the lone Sheriffs on the night
shift encounter a mysterious man who goes by the name of Mr.
As the night progresses, the Sheriffs discover that this isn't just a nobody,
but a vengeful killer whose past threatens to haunt them all.
Jack Hawkins, played by John Cassini.
Mr. Nobody / Drifter, played by Val Kilmer.
Deputy Jane Hollow, played by Camille Sullivan.
Detective Alexander Black, played by Dylan Neal.
Deputy Jerry Pine, played by Paul McGillion.
Desk Sargeant Gulloy, played by Chris Gauthier.
The Traveler is a 2010 American–Canadian direct-to-video horror film
directed by Michael Oblowitz written by Joseph C.
Muscat, and starring Val Kilmer and Dylan Neal.
Kilmer plays a stranger who walks into a small town's police station, confesses to
murder, and is interrogated by detective Alexander Black (Neal).
The film explores themes of suffocation, series of murders,
haunted by the past, police department, christmas.
The tone is dark and intense.